<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_tablemaker</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>1.2.0</version>
		<addition>
			<item>[PRO] Support for tab seperated files</item>
		</addition>
		<change>
			<item>Lookup now has its own tab with parameters</item>
			<item>HTML now has its own tab with parameters</item>
		</change>
		<remove>
			<item>[J3] Remove support for Joomla 3.10</item>
		</remove>
	</changelog>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_tablemaker</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>1.1.0</version>
		<addition>
			<item>[J5] Native support for Joomla 5</item>
			<item>Added support for upgrading from Tablemaker for CSV (opening the module is still required)</item>
		</addition>
		<change>
			<item>Download ID should now be entered in the manifest per Joomla standard (no longer in the Gileba Framework plugin)</item>
			<item>[J3] Support for Joomla 3.10 is deprecated; Support for Joomla 3.9 and lower is removed</item>
		</change>
	</changelog>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_tablemaker</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>1.0.2</version>
		<fix>
			<item>[J4] Make sure jQuery is loaded when Pagination or Lookup is enabled</item>
			<item>[J4] Remove joomlaimage information from URL</item>
			<item>Fix typo in variable name of the new paramater "color of the active pagination item".</item>
		</fix>
	</changelog>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_tablemaker</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>1.0.1</version>
		<addition>
			<item>Added option to set the color of the active pagination item (previously only the backgroundcolor could be set).</item>
		</addition>
		<change>
			<item>The field to set the minimum number of characters for a lookup in the table is now placed under the option to activate the lookup. It will only show when that option is enabled.</item>
		</change>
		<fix>
			<item>All ID attributes now contain the ID of the module to be unique in case the module is used more than once on a page. This fixes a problem where lookup and pagination were not able to perform correctly when two or more modules are rendered on the same page.</item>
			<item>CSS ID-attribute 'csvtable' is only needed when the options lookup or pagination are enabled.</item>
			<item>Added version attribute to the manifest-file of the module.</item>
		</fix>
		<note>
			<item>Some changes in this version might not be backwards compatible with your custom CSS-styling. Check your custom CSS if you have used an id-attribute for styling this module (which is never recommended). All id-attributes have now changed to be unique in a DOM, as per definition.</item>
		</note>
	</changelog>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_tablemaker</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>1.0.0</version>
		<note>
			<item>First release under a new name</item>
		</note>
	</changelog>
</changelogs>
